# **Nguyen Hoang Anh**

# Senior Software Engineer

**>** (+84) 96 322 6061



anhnguyenbk12@gmail.com



III Jan 01 1994



linkedin.com/in/anhnguyenbk12

# Summary

I have more than 4 years experiences in IT industry, love to build high quality products and services. My strong experience is working on Java and Spring frameworks (WebFlux (Reactive), Spring MVC, Spring Security, Spring Batch).

I have experience in building CI/CD pipeline used container-based engine (Docker, Kubernetes).

I eager to learn new technologies and seeking to work with microservices, scalability system.

# **Experiences**

Mar. 2020 - present

Senior Developer, PYCO Group.

#### **Initial & recurring payment system**

- Project description: Initial and retrial recurring charge system for subscribed users (online movies system).
- Team size: 6
- **Responsibility:** Implement features and support on the issues.
- Technologies: Spring WebFlux (Reactive), MongoDB, MySQL, Kafka, Kafka Connector.

Jun. 2018 - Mar. 2020

**Team leader,** SGH Asia.

### **Document Tracking Platform**

- Project description: Build a platform for tracking document (invoice) workflow.
- **Team size:** 3
- **Responsibility:**

Get requirement from production department. Break the tasks and implement the functions.

Weekly build and deploy to QC environment.

• Technologies: Spring Boot 2.x, Spring Security, String MVC, Spring Batch, MongoDB, MySQL, ActiveMQ.

**Developer,** SGH Asia.

#### **SGH Customer Portal**

- **Project description:** Portal for the company's customers
- Team size: 3
- Responsibility:

Develop new features on a new Spring MVC website (current website written in Ruby on Rails)

Migrate Sidekiq background jobs (Ruby) into Spring Batch (Java)

• **Technologies:** Spring MVC, Spring Batch, Ruby on Rails (v3).

#### Feb. 2017 - May. 2018

Java Developer, ELCA Vietnam.

#### A product for insurance

- Project description: Develop a system to manage pensions for Suisse.
- Team size: 15+Duration: 1+ years
- Responsibilities:
  - Developer: Works on back-end services (Java, Hibernate, Spring), API services (gRPC, Protobuf) and front-end (JavaFX).
  - DevOps: Monitoring the project CI pipelines (based on Jenkins and Rundeck), 1 auto test environment and 2 integration test environments as well as analyze and resolve problem arises on them.
- **Technologies:** Java 1.8, Hibernate, Spring (Boot, Clound, Batch), gRPC, Protobuf, JavaFX, SQL Server.

#### Oct. 2016 - Jan. 2017

# Graduation Essay, ELCA Vietnam & Bach Khoa University

- Project description: Build a container-based CI pipeline for the ELCA company.
- Team size: 2
- **Duration:** 5 months
- Responsibilities:
  - Study how to use Docker to facilitate application development, deployment and test.
  - Given solution and construction of a container-based CI pipeline facility for Java EE projects using Docker, OpenShift (based on Kubernetes) and Jenkins.
  - Prove that the Docker solution is lighter and cheaply than traditional VMs in the current ELCA's pipeline.
- Technologies: Docker, OpenShift, Jenkins.

#### 2016

### Freelance Web Developer

#### A travel website

- **Project description:** Build a website that provides travel tours of Dalat, Vietnam for a business. The website iscurrently available at <a href="https://dalattrongtoi.com">https://dalattrongtoi.com</a>.
- Team size: 1
- **Duration:** 6 months
- Responsibilities:
  - Work with the client on the project requirements.
  - Implement for functions.
- Technologies: PHP 5.6, Codeigniter, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular JS, MySQL.

# Other experiences

#### Sep. 2020 - present

### **Trading platform**

- **Project description:** Stock and crypto trading bot based on technical indicators.
- **Responsibility:** Build and simulation trading bots according to technical strategy (based on technical indicators).

• Technologies: Python, TA-lib.

### **Skills**

- Programing Languages: Java, JavaScript, React, PHP, Ruby, Python
- Databases: MS-SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB
- Frameworks: Spring family, Hibernate, Laravel, Rails, Flask, Express
- Middle: RabbitMQ, ActiveMQ, Kafka
- CI/CD, Container-based (Docker), Kubernetes
- Linux
- Responsive Web Design
- Cloud Computing (AWS)
- REST, Protobuf

### **Education**

Sep. 2012 - Apr. 2017

Bach Khoa University (BKU), Computer Science, 7.79

# Languages

• Vietnamese: Mother tongue

• English: Intermediate